const STORE = [{
    question: 'What was the profession of William Morrison, the inventor of machine-spun cotton candy?',
    answers: [
        'Baker',
        'Electrician',
        'Plumber',
        'Dentist'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Dentist'
},

{
    question: 'Which country commonly refers to the dessert course as "Pudding"?',
    answers: [
        'England',
        'Canada',
        'Australia',
        'New Zealand'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'England'
},
{
    question: 'Approximately how many chocolate chip cookies are consumed annually in America?',
    answers: [
        '7 billion',
        '250 million',
        '1 billion',
        '500 million'
    ],
    correctAnswer: '7 billion'
},
{
    question: 'Which dessert is most missed by astronauts on space flights?',
    answers: [
        'cookies',
        'pie',
        'birthday cake',
        'ice cream'

    ],
    correctAnswer: 'ice cream'
},
{
    question: 'What is the price of the most expensive ice cream sundae in the world?',
    answers: [
        '$300',
        '$999.99',
        '$20,000',
        '$25,000'
    ],
    correctAnswer: '$25,000'
},
{
question: 'Of the following, which answer correctly explains why a baker\'s dozen is 13?',
answers: [
    'In case one is ruined',
    'Because the baker is being nice',
    'So the weight of the items will be sufficient',
    'Because the baker can\'t count properly'
],
correctAnswer: 'So the weight of the items will be sufficient'
},

{
question: 'German Chocolate cake originated from which country?',
answers: [
    'England',
    'Germany',
    'Austria',
    'America'
],
correctAnswer: 'America'
},
{
question: 'This Spanish custard is traditionally topped with caramel sauce:',
answers: [
    'Leche Frita',
    'Flan',
    'Arroz con Leche',
    'Magdalenas'

],
correctAnswer: 'Flan'
},
{
question: 'A custard dessert with a hard shell of burned sugar on top:',
answers: [
    'Crème caramel',
    ' Pot de crème',
    'Flan',
    'Crème brûlée'

],
correctAnswer: 'Crème brûlée'
},
{
question: 'When you flambé a dessert, you:',
answers: [
    'Cook it over low heat until thick',
    'Add alcohol to the pan and light it with fire',
    'Cover it with sugar and caramelize it with a kitchen torch',
    'Brown it under the broiler after baking'
],
correctAnswer: 'Add alcohol to the pan and light it with fire'
}
];